ZAK GOGI

Profile

My name is Zak Gogi and I am a Maths graduate from the University of Leeds, currently working as a data contractor for Beauhurst. As a Mathematics student I am an excellent problem solver, have good numerical skills, am able to communicate ideas clearly and am a quick learner. I have experience through my degree using Python, and on my own time I've learned and used Javascript and HTML/CSS on professional projects.

Education and Qualifications

University of Leeds(2016-2019)

Bsc (Hons) Mathematics. Achieved a 2:1.

Modules including - Financial mathematics 1 & 2 (including excel), Computational Mathematics (python specific), Real Analysis, Fluid dynamics, Special Relativity, Code Theory.

Completed my dissertation project on particle simulation using high order integration completely modelled and coded using python. I produced images of different particle setups over time and generated large volumes of random numbers to properly emulate the particle movement process.

Dunraven School(2008-2015)

A Levels: maths - A*, further maths - B, physics - B, AS levels: history - B, economics - B 13 GCSEs - 8A*'s, 4A's and 1 B including Maths and English

Professional Experience

Software Engineering Project - Self Employed (Sep 2019 - March 2020)

- Sole engineer on a project creating a booking system for local sports pitches, primarily using google script which mirrors javascript and html/css.
- Automating the booking process with a user-friendly form that autofills existing customer details, ensures no overlaps in bookings by excluding times that have been occupied at certain pitches and is tailored specifically to client requests such as placing booked events in a separate Google Calendar for specific customer names.
- Incorporates custom menu bar features in excel that allow data to be sent in a precise manner to the accountant of the company.
- Ongoing technical support with any potential problems with the product, and in constant contact about advancing the product further

Beauhurst Data Contractor (July 2020 - June 2021)

- Analysing data through Beauhurst backend software, and researching specific companies to ensure they satisfy Beauhurst determined metrics to identify high growth companies.
- Creating profiles for these companies that are developed into profiles seen by consumers of Beauhurst platform.
- Making quick but quality decisions on different aspects of the Beauhurst backend process involving company details.

Futureproof Trainee Full Stack Developer (June 2021 - Sept 2021)

- 13-week bootcamp covering the main areas of web development, including JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Databases, and Python
- Consistently working collaboratively on paired programming projects, as well as in larger groups to create products to be presented to senior Futureproof team members.

Additional Interests and Extracurricular

In my spare time I'm currently investing in the American small cap market, as well as crypto, and have tried my hand at both intraday trading and long term investing. I've attended the CogX convention as a volunteer and attended multiple talks about the future of the tech industry. I've also worked on a few personal code related projects throughout lockdown, from an endless runner game using unity, built with a c++ engine, to creating a basic python chatbot, to using an API and pythons pandas library to create an equal weighted version of the S&P 500. Check out my other projects on the projects page.